[rock music]
♪ ♪
Welcome to the West Texas
Nature Preserve. mm-kay?
So before we get started.
interesting fact:
We're just
a few hundred feet away
from the New Mexico border.
which is in the Mountain
Time Zone.
So if you go up the road
just a bit.
it's an hour earlier.
Whoa.
So we can. like.
travel through time?
Well. no.
That's not how it works.
It's just a different time zone.
Whoa.
Did you hear that. Beavis?
He said we can travel
to future time zones.
Cool. yeah. yeah.
[both laugh]
Let's go.
Now.
if you keep your eyes peeled.
you can see up to two kinds
of cactus.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Well. Beavis.
on the other side of that sign
lies an hour in the future.
Whoa.
- [laughs]
A place few people will ever go.
Well. here we are.
Cool.
It feels advanced or something.
So. um. so what do you wanna do
here in the future?
Uh. let's go in there
and get a hot dog.
[laughs]
- Um. I'm not hungry yet.
Uh. then let's go another
hour in the future
when it's lunchtime.
Oh. yeah. Good idea. yeah.
This is cool.
- Just go around here.
It's gonna be cool.
[laughs]
There we go.
Yeah. that's better.
Yeah. now I'm starving.
I think.
This hot dog is full
of things not known
to our time.
[chuckles]
Oh. damn it.
Don't worry. Beavis.
We can just. like.
go back in time an hour
to before it got the germs
on it.
Oh. yeah. yeah. Yeah. cool.
[chortles]
[both laugh]
There we go.
It's amazing no one else
has thought of this.
Most people are stupid. Beavis.
It's a fact.
- Yeah. yeah.
Yeah. that's better.
No germs.
Hey. you gotta pay for those.
Uh. sir. don't worry.
In the future.
we will get some money.
and then we will go back in time
and pay for this an hour ago.
Remember? [laughs]
- Ow! [grunts]
- Damn it.
Boy. for a guy in the future.
he doesn't understand
time travel.
Yeah. yeah.
Yeah. I thought people
in the future
were supposed to be smart.
Jesus.
[Jacob Sartorius' "Chapstick"]
♪ I wore that hoodie
to school this morning ♪
[laughs]
White people.
[chuckles]
This is like a boy band.
but with just one person. yeah.
Yeah. and he actually is a boy.
Yeah. he looks like he's 11.
[both laugh]
Yeah. check this out. Butt-Head.
[laughs] Yeah.
Yeah. I mean. yeah. this kid.
he's young. you know?
You know. and he says like. uh.
"Hey. you wanna come back
to my crib?"
He means an actual crib.
you know what I'm saying?
He's young. you know?
[laughs]
You're in rare form today. Beavis.
Yeah. I mean. I don't wanna
say he's young. but. uh.
you know. this chick thinks
he's got wood.
but it's just
his diaper's full. you know?
And he's young.
this kid. you know?
Hey-yo!
[both laugh]
♪ Nothing between us
but Chapstick ♪
Uh. isn't it. like.
illegal for a girl her age
to be with a kid his age?
[chortles]
- Yeah. yeah. really.
He's a victim.
[laughs]
[chuckles]
He's wearing headphones.
so he doesn't have to listen
to this crap.
Yeah. they should let us listen
to whatever he's listening to.
They're playing Mozart
to help
with his brain development.
[both laugh]
Yeah. it's not working.
♪ Between us but Chapstick ♪
"Nothing between us
but Chapstick."
what's that even mean?
Well. I'll tell you one thing
that's not between 'em.
pubic hair.
[both laugh]
Uh. come on. Butt-Head.
That's kind of mean.
Uh. I don't care.
He's rich.
and he gets
to score when he's 11.
[chuckles]
He'll be just fine.
[laughs]
Uh. let's go to the future
and see if future chicks have.
like. loosened up any
about wanting to score.
Um. I'm gonna go backwards.
so I don't go too far
into the future.
I don't wanna get. like.
eaten by a robot or something.
Uh. good thinking. Beavis.
- Aah. aah!
- [laughs]
Uh. damn it.
I think I broke my arm.
Butt-Head.
[cracks] Ow.
Nothing to worry about. Beavis.
Let's just go back an hour
to before you broke it.
Oh. yeah. yeah. Ow.
Yeah. I think it feels better
or something.
Yeah. [laughs]
Ow.
Whoa. check it out. Beavis.
Future chicks.
I can drive until we get
to Midland if you want.
Uh. hey. future baby.
[laughs]
[arm cracks]
We're from. like. a bygone era.
We would like to score with you.
- [laughs]
- In the future.
Oh. my God.
what happened to your arm?
Oh. um.
I'm gonna break it later.
Yeah.
It's really gonna hurt
in an hour.
Whoa. I gotta sit down here.
Damn it. Beavis.
You're messing up my game.
Let's go back in time an hour
and do this again.
And don't screw it up this time.
Okay. okay. yeah.
Now this time let me do all
the talking. dumbass.
Hey. thanks for the coffee. hon.
Now what do we do. Butt-Head?
It's like we went too far back
in time
to when they had boyfriends
or something.
Beavis. mark my words:
we will travel through time
until we find the part
of human history
where we can score.
Oh. yeah. yeah.
[laughs]
Boi-oi-oi... ahh!
We just have to keep going
back in time
until before those chicks met
their boyfriends.
[laughs]
- Um. okay. yeah.
Um. think we're there yet?
Uh. probably. [laughs]
Just a little further
to make sure.
I just wanna be careful
not to go too far back
to. like. before they were born.
I'm gonna go back in time
to before you were born
and do your mom.
That's not funny. Butt-Head.
Come on. Don't do that.
- [laughs]
- I'm gonna be your dad.
Yeah. shut up!
Come back here!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Run along. little Beavis.
Your mother and I need
some alone time.
Stop going back in time.
butthole!
Come here!
Whoa. I'm getting dizzy.
Must be the time travel.
I'm gonna kick your ass.
Quit moving around in circles.
Son of a bitch.
- [grunts]
Ow. ow. ow. my arm! Ahh. ahh!
- Uh. damn it.
- [chuckles]
Um. uh. Butt-Head?
Where are we?
Where's that sign?
Uh. it's gone.
[laughs]
Beavis.
we're trapped in the past.
Oh. boy. [laughs]
[light music]
Oh. cool. yeah.
Yeah. Shark Week kicks ass.
[laughs]
It sure does.
You know what I always wondered?
Where is the shark's butt.
you know?
You just don't see anything
back there. you know?
Well. I'm glad you asked. Beavis.
The bull shark
doesn't have a butt.
It has an anus.
which is located
in the sub-schlongal region.
[laughs]
Just near
the testicular mesiphries.
[chuckles]
Oh. wow.
Wow. that's interesting.
Butt-Head.
How do you know so much
about sharks?
Uh. sometimes
when I'm watching Shark Week.
I. like.
pay attention and stuff.
Like. did you know at one time
75% of the Earth's surface
was covered with sharks?
Whoa. really?
Yeah. I don't know.
That seems like a lot.
Butt-Head.
It's true. Beavis.
And if they ever stop swimming.
they score.
[laughs]
- Really?
I mean. why do they swim at all?
It is a mystery. Beavis.
We don't know.
Also. a shark can go
like six months without water.
That's amazing.
You know what I don't
understand is. um.
they always have. like.
those little fish
that are. like. following 'em
around. you know?
Like. right on their wings
or whatever.
Their scientific name
is the Beavis Fish.
[laughs]
Also known as the Wuss Fish.
Much like the Land Beavis.
it follows around someone
much cooler than itself.
[laughs]
Shut up. Butt-Head! Come on.
This fish has another thing
in common with you. Beavis.
The Beavis Fish's mom is known
as the notorious Slut Fish.
Come on. Butt-Head. Come on.
It has done it
with whales. octopuses.
penguins. drowning dudes.
the bottom of a boat.
you name it.
If it swims. she'll do it.
Come on. Butt-Head.
That's enough.
Uh. okay. just one more.
[chuckles]
No. Butt-Head. Come on.
You're gonna thank me. Beavis.
It's a good one.
Okay. okay. okay.
One more and that's all.
She turned the coral reef
into the oral reef.
[both laugh]
Yeah. yeah.
I guess you were right.
Butt-Head.
[both laugh]
Oral reef. [laughs]
So. like. um. where's the bus?
I think the bus
hasn't been invented yet.
[both laugh]
- Damn it.
That sucks.
How are we gonna get home?
Our home is gone. dumbass.
I think we went back
like a hundred years
to caveman times.
Yeah. well. um. let's go find
a cave to live in.
Maybe one that has a TV
or something.
[laughs]
I'm gonna score with a gorilla.
And I'm gonna invent fire. yeah.
I'm gonna score
with that long-time-ago chick
with the leaf on her thingy.
Um. can I score
with the gorilla then?
[laughs]
Uh. no.
I get both.
Damn it. That sucks.
I know it's late.
but we can't leave
until everyone is on the bus.
Has anyone seen Beavis
and Butt-Head?
No one has seen Beavis
Not one person?
Come on. guys. Think.
Not one person's seen
Beavis and Butt-Head?
[rock music]
♪ ♪
Chirp.